Everyone has a side they
don't show anyone else.
To their friends, their significant others,
or even their families.
They hide what they're truly feeling
through fake smiles or bravado,
and keep their true identities secret.
That is how the world keeps up
the appearance of its temporary peace.
In an era in which the nations of
the world were waging a fierce war
of information just out of sight,
two countries were at odds with each other.
Ostania, in the east, was secretly
plotting to start a war.
Westalis, in the west, wanted to
put a stop to those plans.
In order to keep an eye on the actions of a
leading figure in Ostania's government,
Westalis set Operation Strix in motion.
The one tasked with this operation
is the skilled agent, Twilight.
The mission given to the master of
disguise with a hundred faces was...
to start a family.
128 Park Avenue, West District
Capital City of Berlint, Ostania
Is this everything you own?
Yes.
It's not very much.
Um, Loid... about the
sleeping arrangements...
We'll be sleeping in
separate rooms, of course.
We'll share one for appearances
anytime we have guests over.
R-Right.
Welcome to Anya's house!
Thank you for the lovely welcome, Miss Anya.
This house is home to
a rather unusual family.
The father, Loid Forger, is a psychiatrist.
His true identity: a spy.
Code Name
<Twilight>
Code name: Twilight.
The mother, Yor Forger, is a civil
servant who works at city hall.
Her true identity: an assassin.
Code Name
<Thorn Princess>
Code name: Thorn Princess.
The daughter, Anya Forger.
Her true identity: a telepath.
I'm so happy to have a mama now!
Mama...
I'm gonna help.
Oh, right. By the way...
I had a friend of mine who's a judge
make it so we got married a year ago.
By that, I mean he forged the certificate.
We can figure out why we lived separately
and what to tell your brother later.
All right.
It would make the school suspicious if we
got married just before the interview.
I got permission from the Shopkeeper,
so I feel much better.
So exciting...
Father, mother, daughter...
These three created this pretend
family to further their own ends,
and are living under the same roof as they
hide their true identities from each other.
PREPARE FOR THE INTERVIEW
I'm going to show Mama around!
Once we get settled in,
we'll practice the interview.
This is the kitchen!
Papa is good at cooking!
Oh, I see.
This is the toilet. And that's the bathtub!
Everything's so clean.
I can wash my face all by myself!
You're such a big girl, Miss Anya.
This is Anya's room!
Welcome!
Thank you for inviting me in.
My, what an adorable room.
I'll introduce you to Mr. Chimera.
I am Chimera. It is a pweasure
to meet your acquiantenance.
It's very nice to meet you, Mr. Chimera.
I am Miss Anya's mama.
This is Papa's room!
So this is Loid's room...
This is your room, Mama.
Come in, Mama.
Why, thank you.
So this is my...
What a lovely room.
I'm glad you like it.
This should be everything.
Is the furniture arranged to
your liking? I also cleaned a bit.
Yes, everything is wonderful.
I helped clean, too!
Really? Thank you so much.
Am I a good girl?
All you did was tip over a bucket of water.
Shock!
This is such a lovely room. I don't
know what to do with myself.
What do you mean?
Please make yourself at home.
Actually, this is your home now,
so make yourself comfortable.
Thank you.
I'll come get your boxes once they're empty.
Loid, I've got everything put away.
You're quite efficient.
Ah, this must be your younger brother.
Oh, yes.
You said he's also a civil servant?
Yes. He seems quite busy lately,
so I've only spoken to him on the phone.
It seems you two are quite similar.
I should properly introduce myself
once Anya's entrance exam is over.
Um, Loid. About that...
I don't have anything suitable
to wear to this interview...
Then let's go to the tailor today.
Thank you very much.
Helping, helping...
M-Miss Anya, I'll take care of that!
I have my work weapons and poison
powerful enough to kill an elephant in there.
Can I get you something, Loid?
Some coffee, please. Black.
I want hot cocoa!
With sugar and milk.
That's the stuff!
They look amazing. Are those cookies homemade?
It's actually my first time making cookies.
I just followed a recipe from a cookbook,
so they should be decent.
I hope you like them.
Thank you.
They're wonderful! You really
are an amazing cook!
It's not that impressive, really.
I helped with the cookies, too!
Oh, I see.
After you got covered in
flour and got in my way,
you just snacked on some peanuts.
Once we're settled in, let's begin.
Eden College is one of the most
prestigious schools in the country.
During the interview, not only
will the child be evaluated,
but so will the parents.
They will be evaluated on their social
standing as well as how cultured they are.
Understood?
Now, let's start the questions.
First, please state your name and address.
Anya Fo...Fo...Horger. Address?
The place we're at right now.
This is Anya's house!
That's not what I meant.
Er, so, Miss Anya... How do
you spend your days off?
Papa orders me to stay home,
so I have to watch TV all alone.
Now, wait a second.
That makes a terrible impression. Madam?
Yes?
Why did you choose Eden College,
and how do you plan to pass this exam?
How do people usually pass?
Um, pass, passing...
Perhaps because of cardiac arrest,
or excessive bleeding?
Or compound fractures throughout the body?
Oh! Maybe their skull was caved in.
Kill me now. Next question.
Could you describe your parenting methods?
Huh? U-Um... Strike first to be victorious?
I'm amazed her brother turned
out to be a decent human being.
I've been a spy for over a decade.
I've completed countless missions,
yet only now do I find myself losing heart.
This is pointless. There's no way we'll
survive the interview at this rate.
Let's give up on getting
her into that school.
Loid! Please remember
your late wife's wishes!
Clearly, we weren't ready
for this mock interview yet.
All right, let's go out for a bit.
Let's broaden our horizons, become versed
in what is normal for an upper-class family,
and make sure that we're
all on the same page.
We're on an ooting,
an ooting, la, la, la, lah!
You mean "outing."
Wanna hold hands, Mama?
I-If you don't mind.
Thank goodness Anya's taken a liking to her.
The plan is set.
After today, we'll seem like a normal... no.
We'll be seen as an upper-crust family.
Oh... This reminds me of when my little
brother was still small and adorable.
And that one time I hugged him too hard
and ended up breaking two of his ribs.
I must be careful.
Wait... what? Maybe not...
B-By the way, where are we headed?
I've acquired a variety of tickets
through my connections at work.
Tradition and status are
everything at Eden College.
We'll have to experience and get accustomed
to the best that life has to offer,
and make sure we don't slip
up if we let our guard down.
All right, next.
Anya, no yelling while we're here.
'Kay.
We've experienced first-class music,
so now for some first-class art...
And you know the rest.
Papa! I can see her boobies!
Head's been choppy-chopped!
Body's been choppy-chopped!
What did I just say about yelling?
Yor?
Y-Yor...?
I wanna do that!
Drawing? Sure.
Yor, why don't we sit down for a bit?
All right.
Anya's house is a big castle.
The boss of the secret organization
is Director Chimera.
Papa is a spy! Pew, pew!
Mama is an assassin!
Stabby, stabby, sploosh!
We should probably get going.
Yes.
All done!
Anya, we're going to our next stop.
If Papa and Mama see this,
they'll find out about my powers!
Wow, that's quite a masterpiece.
There seems to be a pig in a forest.
That's Mr. Chimera, and he lives in a castle!
I see. I definitely see
Bondman there, though.
I'm right, aren't I?
Yep...
It's that spy cartoon you
were watching last week.
So this witch-looking one
must be the princess.
That part seems rather graphic.
Oh, but that cat is cute.
That's a doggy!
I see. Then I apologize.
We're going to the tailor next.
Sorry to have you do this on your day off.
It's quite all right. This is
something we need to do.
My going-out clothes are so cute!
They fit perfectly!
This shop is great! I love it!
Why, thank you.
This is my first ooting
in my going-out clothes.
Then it must be a day of celebration.
A day to celebrate this ooting!
In that case, we can stop by
a photography studio next.
Yor, dear. Right this way.
Coming.
If you're looking for a semi-formal dress,
I think this color would do nicely.
What do you think?
I'd honestly prefer a black or red dress.
Really? I think this would
look nice on you, Yor.
Then how about this?
Judging from her lack of luggage,
I thought she had no interest in clothes.
I see you're particular
about matching colors.
No... I wouldn't say that.
This color's lovely, but I'm worried that
blood splatters would be too noticeable.
Looks like Yor finally found someone nice.
Hopefully they last. Having a child
already is an instant no for me, though.
Looks like the extra outfits will
be ready by the interview, too.
I'm so sorry to have you get so many.
Well, you look nice in
colors besides red and black.
We'll be going out more often, too.
Ootings! Ootings!
You're a regular at that shop, aren't you?
I'm sure we'll continue to shop there, so next
time, we should tell them we're married.
Oh, right.
We, the Nationalist Party, believe that
there is a road to peace with the West.
Patriotism is also important within Eden.
You moron!
Kill all the bastards in the West!
Continuing to treat Westalis as
the enemy will do us no good.
I'll need to make sure she's knowledgeable
of politics and history, as well.
Piss off, traitor!
Gimme money, gimme money, gimme money...
Those bastards killed my family!
Get lost with the pleasantries!
First I lost my job, then my home!
What's the matter?
I don't like places like this...
Kill all the shitheads in the West!
Sorry. Maybe this was a
little scary for you.
Let's go rest somewhere.
The East did nothing wrong!
Go back to your Western masters!
Damn it!
You pig!
You stupid baldy!
Your feet smell, too!
Papa, I'm hungry.
Huh?
Are you all right or not?
No, Anya. Don't just pick the nuts off
the top, and no eating with your hands.
And Yor, uh... Hmm...
I've been a spy for over a decade.
I've completed countless missions,
yet once again I find myself losing heart.
S'all good, Papa.
What is?
Yeah, I definitely picked the wrong child.
No, this is all because I was
expected to rely on others.
I shouldn't have put the key to success in
the hands of others, let alone civilians.
Predicting every possible
situation, preparing for it,
and acting from a carefully laid-out plan.
Those are the ironclad rules of being a spy.
Which means that I need to list every
possible question the interviewer can ask,
then have these two memorize the
perfect answers to go with them.
If all else fails, make sure
I can back them up—
Um...
Why don't we go get some fresh air?
The people look like bits
of trash from up here.
Where did you get that from?
My cartoons.
Ah...
I had no idea there was a park like
this on the outskirts of town.
I don't come here that often either,
but I wander over here when
I'm exhausted from work.
Thinking about how the work I do
helps everyone in this city out
encourages me to work harder.
Oh, this place must be awfully
boring! I'm terribly sorry!
I like this place better
than crowded places!
Oh, that's wonderful!
Thief! Someone help!
That old lady should've been more careful.
You won't get away with this!
Hold it right there!
Oh, damn it.
I lost track of him.
Are you all right, ma'am? Are you hurt?
I'm fine. Just a few scratches.
I promise I'll catch him for you!
And I'll take you to the hospital later!
Why, thank you.
I left Loid and Anya behind.
He blended in with the crowd.
I'm very sorry, Yor, but you probably
won't be able to find him now.
Man, I'm starving.
So expensive...
Aw, this is so cute.
Crap, I'm gonna piss my pants.
My feet hurt.
That shopworker is so cool.
I wonder if there's a million
dalc lying around somewhere.
Oh, I forgot to pay my rent.
Man, he's late.
Honestly, this child...
What am I going to do? I failed my test again.
That bastard. I'm gonna murder him.
Maybe I'll say hi...
Hey, this again?
Man, that old crone was loaded.
Papa!
Whoa, what?
I wanna eat cake!
What?!
We just left the restaurant...
He's...
He changed his clothes, but it's not
so easy to change the way you walk.
Don't think you'll get away from me.
Loid!
Mama's here.
Yor, look after Anya for me.
I'll be able to have plenty of
fun for a while with this much.
First, I'm gonna treat myself
to the finest meal and—
A filthy swine like you deserves
nothing more than the foulest meal.
What's going on?
A guy just dropped from the sky.
A spy must not bring attention to himself.
Did he fall?
Pardon me. This fellow is a purse snatcher,
so please call the police and hand him over.
A purse snatcher?
Thank you for escorting
me all the way here.
I had money to get my grandchild
a gift in my purse.
Thank you so much. You were a big help.
Oh, actually...
The one who got it back
was my, um, husband.
No, if you weren't there, Yor,
I wouldn't have even gone after him.
Thank you so much. What a
fine gentleman you are.
Er, again...
Hero who casts no shadow,
the great deeds you and your fellow
agents do shall never see the light of day.
Thank you.
I guess... receiving thanks every
once in a while wouldn't hurt.
Papa is a softie.
Thank you, Yor.
Today was a nice change of pace.
Now I'll be able to work hard again.
Papa and Mama are flirting.
We are not!
Does Anya get a thank you, too?
Well... I guess we did find the thief
because you were hungry again.
Good girl.
My, what a lovely family you are.
Here's some candy for you, dear.
Candy!
Make sure you say, "Thank you."
The ooting is over!
What a long day.
Mama!
I want some hot cocoa, please!
As you wish.
Hey, more importantly, we need
to retry this mock interview.
So, Miss Anya, how do you
spend your days off?
We go to the opera, the museum,
and eat at restaurants.
Yes! Exactly!
If you're asked this question,
make sure you talk about today.
Okay, next question.
You've seen your friend
do something naughty.
What will you do?
I'd jump on top of them, beat them up,
and make them eat the foulest meal!
Hmm... Pretend you never saw that, okay?
Yup, this is hopeless. I'm done.
Papa, you were so cool!
Yes, he was.
Ka-bam!
It's the foulest meal for you!
Hot cocoa is the best.
My, what a lovely family you are.
I guess if she saw us that way...
About one percent of my
preparations are complete.
THE PRESTIGIOUS SCHOOL'S INTERVIEW